Hari Sharma fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Community activism records, 1968 - 2008; F-251-3; 4.12 m of textual records
  - Indian People's Association in North America files, 1973 - 1995; F-251-3-3; 74 cm of textual records; Language: Some notes in Hindi. Also contains publications in Punjabi and French.; Indian People's Association in North America
    - Public release regarding Consulate General's refusal to let Hari Sharma travel to India, 1990; F-251-3-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 251-26)
    - IPANA - misc. correspondence, 1985 - 1995; F-251-3-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 251-26)
    - Babari Masjid - IPANA response, 1990 - 1993; F-251-3-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 251-26)
  - Consulting case files, 1989 - 2006; F-251-3-4; 12 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to Hari Sharma's consulting work on legal cases, immigration and refugee board hearings, and workers' compensation cases predominantly for members of the South Asian community. Includes notes, correspondence, reports, lists, articles, testimonies, claims, and copies of legal documents.
    - Wrongful termination: R. Rai, 1989; F-251-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration Hearing: Kahlon, 1989; F-251-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration case: P.K. Sumra, [199-?]; F-251-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Sumra Case, 1990; F-251-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - S. Nayar refugee case, 1991 - 1992; F-251-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration cases listed, 1992 - 2006; F-251-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration research, notes, 1993 - 1995; F-251-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration: Rai, 1993 - 1995; F-251-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Testimonies/misc., 1993 - 2000; F-251-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Grewal case, 1994 - 1995; F-251-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Immigration: Badial, 1994 - 1995; F-251-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Marriage in Punjabi Culture; Regarding J.K. Badial, 1995; F-251-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Rattu/Ahir, 1995 - 1996; F-251-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - B. Dhillon/Kamloops - WCB, 1996; F-251-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - S.R. Ahir - WCB, 1996; F-251-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - I. Chandra/Chaurasia, 1998; F-251-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - B. Malhotra, 1999 - 2000; F-251-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - G. Chahal, 2001; F-251-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - Refugee case: K. Jalhan, 2002; F-251-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
    - H. Saggu, 2006; F-251-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-27)
  - NRISAD-SANSAD files, 1988 - 2007; F-251-3-5; 1.25 m of textual records; Language: Some personal correspondence, notes, announcements, and publications in Hindi.; Non-Resident Indians for Secularism and Democracy
    The Non-Resident Indians for Secularism and Democracy (NRISAD) was formed by Hari Sharma following the attack on Bari Masjid in December 1992. The organization united people of Indian origin collectively through educational and cultural activities. One of its significant events in Vancouver included the celebration of the 50th anniversary of India's independence from colonial rule. Over time, NRISAD recognized a need to widen the focus of the organization to include the whole of South Asia because its membership in Vancouver comprised people from the entire subcontinent of India and the diaspora in East Africa and other countries. Under Sharma's leadership, NRISAD evolved into the South Asian Network for Secularism and Democracy based secularism, human rights, and social justice.
    Sub-series consists of the organizational records of Non-Resident Indians for Secularism and Democracy (NRISAD) and its successor organization South Asian Network for Secularism and Democracy (SANSAD). Includes records created, made, and/or received by Hari Sharma while serving on several committees within the organization that carried out educational and cultural activities to uphold the secular and democratic values and to oppose the agenda of extreme forces in India. Sub-series includes articles, emails, research notes, statements, flyers, notices, statements, advertisements, incoming and outgoing correspondence, brochures, tickets, programs, minutes, publications, reviews, and photographs.
    Non-Resident Indians for Secularism and Democracy; South Asian Network for Secularism and Democracy; Textual records
    - Saeed Mirza, 1988 - 1997; F-251-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Air India terror (forwarded emails and published articles compiled by Sharma), 1989 - 2007; F-251-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Agriculture Business / Bio-technology (research materials), 1990 - 1994; F-251-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Boylan, [ca 1991]; F-251-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Shabana souvenirs, 1992 - 1994; F-251-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Responses to NRISAD (Sangh Parivar, etc.), 1993; F-251-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - NRISAD: Statement (published), 1993; F-251-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Signature campaign, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - NRISAD: Praful - Rafeeq - To India, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - NRISAD: Correspondence, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Hindutava Ads, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - Accounts: NRISAD, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-28)
    - NRISAD Update (On public statement issued May 25-28, 1993), F-251-3-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - NRISAD: India (responses to advertisement), 1993; F-251-3-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - NRISAD: Vancouver and activities, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - India ad responses - business interests, 1993; F-251-3-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - NRISAD - misc: VHP/NY/North America, 1993 - 1994; F-251-3-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - Shabana, 1993 - 1994; F-251-3-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - NRISAD (related to India) correspondence, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - Aijaz Ahmad, 1993 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-29)
    - NRISAD Accounts - 1994, F-251-3-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - NRISAD Brochure - graphics/text, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana Ticket Sales, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana Dinner (25/September), 1994; F-251-3-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA/Shabana: Ads/Publicity, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana Films, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana - mobilization, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana: Posters/Postcards/Tickets, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shabana: Day-to-day program, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA - stalls/tables, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA - culture, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-31 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - NRISAD: Halls - Tickets/Sales, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-32 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA-sports, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-33 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - NRISAD-India Mela-Letters-Publicity, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-34 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA program correspondence, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-35 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - MELA: 3 guest speakers, 1994; F-251-3-5-0-36 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - NRISAD minutes/meetings, 1994 - 1997; F-251-3-5-0-37 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Shalendra Sharma (publications), 1994 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-38 (Archival box - standard 251-30)
    - Rajni Kothari on Globalization, 1995; F-251-3-5-0-39 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - NRISAD Accounts, 1995 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-40 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - NRISAD 1995 correspondence, 1995 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-41 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - NRISAD activities, 1995 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-42 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - India-Pakistan-Kashmir, 1995 - 2005; F-251-3-5-0-43 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - Habib Tanvir - public meeting, 1996; F-251-3-5-0-44 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - Habib Tanvir correspondence, 1996 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-45 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - Sainath, 1997; F-251-3-5-0-46 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - Tea industry, India, 1997; F-251-3-5-0-47 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - The Fiftieth Year (Aug. 14, 1997, PGM), 1997 - 1998; F-251-3-5-0-48 (Archival box - standard 251-31)
    - M. Mohanty, [ca 1997] - [ca 1998]; F-251-3-5-0-49 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - October 1998 Programs (correspondence, planning), F-251-3-5-0-50 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - NRISAD activities (publicity, announcements), 1998 - 1999; F-251-3-5-0-51 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - Iran/Kurdistan, etc., 1999; F-251-3-5-0-52 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - NRISAD activities (publicity, meeting notes), 1999; F-251-3-5-0-53 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - Panikkar/Deshpande - Summer 1999, F-251-3-5-0-54 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - NRISAD Accounts (June 13, 1998 to May 2, 1999), F-251-3-5-0-55 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - Geetanjali Lal, 1999 - 2000; F-251-3-5-0-56 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - INSAF Montreal Declaration, 1999 - 2001; F-251-3-5-0-57 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - SANSAD Accounts (May 14, 2000 to May 13, 2001), F-251-3-5-0-58 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - SANSAD activities, 2000 - 2001; F-251-3-5-0-59 (Archival box - standard 251-32)
    - Talks: Marygrove, Chapel Hill, Chicago, Toronto, 2000 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-60 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - The Second INSAF Conference: Secularism, Democracy & Social Justice in South Asia, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-61 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - INSAF Souvenir, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-62 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - INSAF - SFU matter, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-63 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - INSAF Conference, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-64 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - INSAF Delegate Registration, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-65 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - Narmada Support Group, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-66 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - SANSAD activities, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-67 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - Rebuilding the Left (Vancouver), 2001; F-251-3-5-0-68 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - INSAF correspondence (Second International Conference), 2001; F-251-3-5-0-69 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - Papers from the South Asian Diaspora, Vancouver BC, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-70 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - After 9-11/S. Asians, 2001; F-251-3-5-0-71 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - Anand Patwardhan review, 2001 - 2002; F-251-3-5-0-72 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - SANSAD Accounts (May 13, 201 to May 2002), 2001 - 2002; F-251-3-5-0-73 (Archival box - standard 251-33)
    - SAYA (South Asian Youth Alliance), 2002; F-251-3-5-0-74 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - SANSAD Retreat (Sept. 14, 2002), F-251-3-5-0-75 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Hindutva Demystified - Viren Prakash, 2002; F-251-3-5-0-76 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - BC Human Rights Comission, 2002; F-251-3-5-0-77 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Race Riots - Fraser Institute - CAW Forum, 2002; F-251-3-5-0-78 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Salmon Yatra - October 2002, F-251-3-5-0-79 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - K. Parhar (Taxi driver), 2002; F-251-3-5-0-80 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Gujarat Committee: Gujarat Panel (July 20, 2002), F-251-3-5-0-81 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Women's Issues Committee, 2002 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-82 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - International Courts, Hindutava, 2002 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-83 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Gujarat / Fascism: Diaspora, 2002 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-84 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - SANSAD activities, 2002 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-85 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Imam Hussein Memorial Lecture, 2002 - 2003; F-251-3-5-0-86 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Gujarat cargo, 2002 - 2004; F-251-3-5-0-87 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Gujarat genocide (research notes, articles, emails), 2002 - 2004; F-251-3-5-0-88 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - Anti-Imperialism / Vancouver, 2002 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-89 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - SANSAD correspondence, 2002 - 2007; F-251-3-5-0-90 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - ILPS-ICC Meetings, Holland (Feb. 28-March 2, 2003), F-251-3-5-0-91 (Archival box - standard 251-34)
    - IMC/USA conference on post-Gujarat India, Santa Clara (June 28, 2003), F-251-3-5-0-92 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - SANSAD (AGM and other events), 2003; F-251-3-5-0-93 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Starbucks, 2003 - 2004; F-251-3-5-0-94 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - International Indigenous Youth Conference - Vancouver, 2003 - 2004; F-251-3-5-0-95 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Arundhati Roy (misc. publications), 2003 - 2007; F-251-3-5-0-96 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - India: 2004 Elections, F-251-3-5-0-97 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - India: Left parties, etc., [ca 2004]; F-251-3-5-0-98 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Nepal Forum, 2004; F-251-3-5-0-99 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - SANSAD Shariah debate, 2004; F-251-3-5-0-100 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Itrath matter, 2004; F-251-3-5-0-101 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - M. Moore's "Farenheit 911", 2004; F-251-3-5-0-102 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Sun Peaks (Shuswap), 2004; F-251-3-5-0-103 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - World Social Forum, 2004; F-251-3-5-0-104 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Yasser Arafat Dies, 2004; F-251-3-5-0-105 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - SANSAD: June 14, 2004-, 2004 - 2005; F-251-3-5-0-106 (Archival box - standard 251-35)
    - Al Qaida - nuisance (correspondence, articles, notes, responses, etc.), 2004 - 2005; F-251-3-5-0-107 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - ILPS, 2004 - 2005; F-251-3-5-0-108 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Anti-imperialist, Pro-Indian Revolution (notes, publications), 2004 - 2005; F-251-3-5-0-109 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Mexican Farm Workers, 2004 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-110 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Gujarat/Rajasthan Visit 2005, 2004 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-111 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - On Dalits, 2004 - 2007; F-251-3-5-0-112 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Rajasthan Alwar - Chittogarh, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-113 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - G. Omvedt, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-114 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Malaysia - Human Rights, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-115 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Stopwar.ca, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-116 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Bello/Sison/Stop War, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-117 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Coalition Against Genocide - N. Modi (USA), 2005; F-251-3-5-0-118 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Nepal, 2005; F-251-3-5-0-119 (Archival box - standard 251-36)
    - Venezuela / Cuba, 2005 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-120 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD AGM (June 19, 2005), 2005 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-121 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - Vancouver Anti-Imperialism Coalition Status, 2005 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-122 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - California textbooks matter, 2005 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-123 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD website, 2005 - 2006; F-251-3-5-0-124 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - Daya, 2006; F-251-3-5-0-125 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - M. Lebowitz, [ca 2006]; F-251-3-5-0-126 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD listing of files by Hari Sharma, [ca 2006]; F-251-3-5-0-127 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - Concerning Nepal, 2006; F-251-3-5-0-128 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD retreat (gender), 2006; F-251-3-5-0-129 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - Coca Cola in India, [ca 2006]; F-251-3-5-0-130 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD AGM (July 30, 2006), 2006 - 2007; F-251-3-5-0-131 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD AGM (Sept. 23, 2007), F-251-3-5-0-132 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - SANSAD AGM (Oct. 2007 - Resolution), F-251-3-5-0-133 (Archival box - standard 251-37)
    - UNSUNI - M. Sarabhai, 2007; F-251-3-5-0-134 (Archival box - standard 251-37, Optical disc: cd-r OBJ-4041)
      - Darpana Unsuni Excerpts (by Mallika Sarbhaiand and Darpana Academy of Ahmedabad), October 2007; F-251-3-5-0-134-1 (Optical disc: cd-r OBJ-4041, Optical disc: dvd-r OBJ-4042)
  - First Nations-SFU partnership files, 1968 - 2003; F-251-3-6; 1.38 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records arising from Hari Sharma's involvement with the Secwepemc Cultural Education Society of the Shuswap Nation and the Simon Fraser University partnership program. Sub-series includes reports, agreements, notes, statements, correspondence, programs, booklets, newsletters, pamphlets, transcripts, lists, and proposals.
    Secwepemc Cultural Education Society; Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology; Ronald Ignace; Marianne Boelscher Ignace; Textual records
    - Binder: Shuswap/Kamloops Indian Band miscellaneous research - first half, 1968 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Binder: Shuswap/Kamloops Indian Band misc. research - second half, 1978 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Kamloops Indian Reserve Department Plan Appendices, 1970; F-251-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Handbook for B.C. Bands in Moving Towards Indian Control of Indian Education and Understanding the Master Tuition Agreement, 1978; F-251-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Union of British Columbia Indian Chiefs Constitution Bulletin, 1980; F-251-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Kamloops Agency and the Indian Reserve Commission of 1912-1916 - M.A. thesis by Ronald E. Ignace, 1980; F-251-3-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Kamloops Indian Band Index to Financial Statements, 1981; F-251-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-38)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society documents, 1983 - 1995; F-251-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society, Second Annual Report, 1985; F-251-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Correspondence re. post-secondary assistance program for aboriginal students, 1987; F-251-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Shuswap documents, statements, information booklets, [ca 1987] - [ca 1992]; F-251-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Aboriginal Issues (newsletters of the Inter-American Indian Institute, PANA PANA, and UNA-Vancouver; reports), 1987 - 1992; F-251-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Aboriginal Issues: Canada-wide Movement/Campaign (materials from Canadian Alliance in Solidarity with Native Peoples), 1987 - 1993; F-251-3-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Access to Advanced Education and Job Training in British Columbia booklet, 1988; F-251-3-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Draft agreement between SFU and SCES, 1988; F-251-3-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Concept paper: Family Corporations Program of Shuswap Multi-Development Corporation by Robert E. Simon, 1988; F-251-3-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Misc. documents from Kamloops file (re. economic development program, cultural education society, funding, etc.), 1988 - 1991; F-251-3-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-39)
    - Response to Bob A., 1988 - 1997; F-251-3-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - SCES/SFU programming booklets, reports, 1988 - 1998; F-251-3-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Report: Background Data on the new Post-secondary Education Program, 1989; F-251-3-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Report: A Community Economic Study for the Kamloops Indian Band, prepared by the S.L.S. Project Team, [ca 1989]; F-251-3-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society Board Meeting: June 15, 1989, F-251-3-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Secwepemc Cultural Education Society funding proposal, 1989; F-251-3-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Aboriginal Territories of the Shuswap Nation: Report on Ethnographic and Ethnohistorical Sources, by Dr. Marianne Boelscher, 1989; F-251-3-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Copy of A History of the Shuswap Struggle for a Just Recognition of Land Title and Rights, 1989; F-251-3-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Interim Report of Work in Progress: Anthropological Evidence and Expert Opinion Alliance of Tribal Councils - Shuswap Bands by M. Boelscher, 1989; F-251-3-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 251-40)
    - Shuswap research - funds, 1989 - 1990; F-251-3-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Resources relating to issues in aboriginal communities, 1989 - 1994; F-251-3-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Ministry of Native Affiars newsletters and pamphlets, [ca 1989] - [ca 1994]; F-251-3-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Shuswap research - Sketchestn, 1989 - 1994; F-251-3-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
      Restrict in whole
    - Submission to the Provincial Advisory Committee on Post-Secondary Education for Native Learners, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-31 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Report of the Provincial Advisory Committee on Post-Secondary Education for Native Learners, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-32 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - University Education and Economic Well-Being: Indian Achievement and Prospects, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-33 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Towards Linguistic Justice for First Nations, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-34 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - UBC First Nations House of Learning booklet, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-35 (Archival box - standard 251-41)
    - Communities of Learners: A Study of Models of Brokerage and Affiliation between Native Organizations and Public Post Secondary Institutes - Ronand N. McGivern, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-36 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Correspondence to Hari Sharma from Union of B.C. Indian Chiefs, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-37 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-38 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Lheit-Li Governance Organizational chart, [ca 1990]; F-251-3-6-0-39 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Shuswap land holding listing, [199-?]; F-251-3-6-0-40 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Kamloops Indian Band population figures, [199-?]; F-251-3-6-0-41 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Kamloops Indian Band resources, [ca 1990]; F-251-3-6-0-42 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Research notes regarding "Indian education", [199-?]; F-251-3-6-0-43 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Population figure for Shuswap Nation / Salmon Trade Information, [199-?]; F-251-3-6-0-44 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Shuswap Nation Aboriginal Land Title document, [ca 1990]; F-251-3-6-0-45 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Spence's Bridge Protocol - August 1990), F-251-3-6-0-46 (Archival box - standard 251-42)
    - Chiefs of the Secwepemc (Shuswap) Nation Accord, 1990; F-251-3-6-0-47 (Archival box - standard 251-42)